My name's Amy.
Heineike, and I'm a research engineer at Tessl,
so that means I spend my days trying to work out what on earth LLMs are doing,.
I was really searching for a place where I'd get to spend
a lot of time really deeply understanding what was possible with AI.
And I felt like coding would be one of the most interesting domains to do that in.
I really like working on ambiguous problems
It’s not like there's necessarily a playbook for some of these things,
and you are definitely having to make a bet on something that you think
is going to be interesting without knowing for sure how it will play out.
We're in a space that's moving, you know, incredibly quickly.
It feels like a huge privilege to get to be in a place where you've got
enough resources that you can take a bit of a long view of it.
So on the one side, everything's going really fast
and we need to be out there quickly and responding to the world.
On the other hand, we can kind of think a little bit about
where is this going and what will that mean for, customers?
As a researcher, I need really hard problems
and I need a bunch of compute, free tokens,
And then people that I can bounce ideas off of and, get feedback from.
And then I need customers, users who have real guidance on what's important.
We have all of those things in abundance.
As a company that there's some pretty ambitious ideas
about how much we want to grow and kind of seize the opportunity.
And I think with a startup, you are always betting that,
you know, as the company scales, that creates all kinds of opportunities
for new roles or new responsibilities.
We've got all the opportunity in the world there,
you know, we've got positioning right now, we've got capital at the right time.
We're in this incredibly hot and interesting space.
So we've got everything going for us to go just kind of seize a big opportunity.
And then create our own individual stories inside of that.